http://store.guardiandigital.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy.
Menu
Home
Solutions
Cloud Email Security
EnGarde Cloud Email SecurityFully-managed email security platform powered by AI
Advanced Threat ProtectionStop external email threats - protect your business & brand
Multitier Security & Policy ControlsThreat-ready business email protection through layered security
Incident ResponseMitigate damage and reduce recovery time with seamless, automated incident response
Information ProtectionProtect sensitive data with SPF, DKIM and DMARC
By Platform
Office 365 Email SecurityProtect Office 365 against targeted attacks & phishing scams
Google G Suite Email ProtectionFully-Integrated Cloud Email Security and Continuity Makes G Suite Safe for Business
Microsoft Exchange Email Protection Make Exchange Safe for Business with Critical Additional Email Defenses
By Size
Small & Medium BusinessSecure Email with Enterprise-Grade Protection
By Threats
PhishingCombat phishing with comprehensive, real-time protection
Spear PhishingSafeguard business email against targeted spear phishing campaigns
WhalingProtect against deceptive social engineering attacks and email spoofing
MalwareSecure business email against new and sophisticated malware variants
RansomwarePrevent ransomware attacks with comprehensive, multi-layered business email protection
BECProtect against BEC, spear phishing and email spoofing with threat-ready email vigilance
Email VirusesSafeguard business email against polymorphic viruses with next-generation heuristics
Zero Day AttackDefend against emerging threats and zero-day exploits with intuitive real-time technology
Why Guardian Digital
About UsAbout Guardian Digital - who we are & what we do
Our PhilosophyWe provide cutting-edge security, cost-effective solutions and exceptional support
Customer Success StoriesNothing is more important to us than helping our customers succeed.
Media CenterPress coverage, recent blog posts, company resources and more
Resource CenterBrowse our press releases, news stories, customer stories, media highlights, and other Guardian Digital info.
Open Source CommitmentWe are committed to open-source methodologies, collaborative development and transparency
Open Source PhilosophyOur open-source philosophy - development without limits
Open Source AdvantageUnrivaled security through open-source development
The Guardian Digital AdvantageNext-generation business email protection - flexible and fully supported.
Blog
Industry
Real Estate and Title CompaniesSecure Email Against Wire Transfer Fraud
Law FirmsProtect Email Against Cyberattacks and Data Leaks
HospitalitySecure Email Against Phishing and Impersonation Scams
HealthcareSecure Email Against Phishing and Impersonation Scams
FinancialSafeguard Email Against Spear Phishing and Business Email Compromise Attacks
Information TechnologySecure Email Infrastructure with Real-Time Analysis and Advanced Encryption
Partners
Partner ApplicationBecome a Guardian Digital Worldwide Partner
Home
Solutions
Cloud Email Security
EnGarde Cloud Email SecurityFully-managed email security platform powered by AI
Advanced Threat ProtectionStop external email threats - protect your business & brand
Multitier Security & Policy ControlsThreat-ready business email protection through layered security
Incident ResponseMitigate damage and reduce recovery time with seamless, automated incident response
Information ProtectionProtect sensitive data with SPF, DKIM and DMARC
By Platform
Office 365 Email SecurityProtect Office 365 against targeted attacks & phishing scams
Google G Suite Email ProtectionFully-Integrated Cloud Email Security and Continuity Makes G Suite Safe for Business
Microsoft Exchange Email Protection Make Exchange Safe for Business with Critical Additional Email Defenses
By Size
Small & Medium BusinessSecure Email with Enterprise-Grade Protection
By Threats
PhishingCombat phishing with comprehensive, real-time protection
Spear PhishingSafeguard business email against targeted spear phishing campaigns
WhalingProtect against deceptive social engineering attacks and email spoofing
MalwareSecure business email against new and sophisticated malware variants
RansomwarePrevent ransomware attacks with comprehensive, multi-layered business email protection
BECProtect against BEC, spear phishing and email spoofing with threat-ready email vigilance
Email VirusesSafeguard business email against polymorphic viruses with next-generation heuristics
Zero Day AttackDefend against emerging threats and zero-day exploits with intuitive real-time technology
Why Guardian Digital
About UsAbout Guardian Digital - who we are & what we do
Our PhilosophyWe provide cutting-edge security, cost-effective solutions and exceptional support
Customer Success StoriesNothing is more important to us than helping our customers succeed.
Media CenterPress coverage, recent blog posts, company resources and more
Resource CenterBrowse our press releases, news stories, customer stories, media highlights, and other Guardian Digital info.
Open Source CommitmentWe are committed to open-source methodologies, collaborative development and transparency
Open Source PhilosophyOur open-source philosophy - development without limits
Open Source AdvantageUnrivaled security through open-source development
The Guardian Digital AdvantageNext-generation business email protection - flexible and fully supported.
Blog
Industry
Real Estate and Title CompaniesSecure Email Against Wire Transfer Fraud
Law FirmsProtect Email Against Cyberattacks and Data Leaks
HospitalitySecure Email Against Phishing and Impersonation Scams
HealthcareSecure Email Against Phishing and Impersonation Scams
FinancialSafeguard Email Against Spear Phishing and Business Email Compromise Attacks
Information TechnologySecure Email Infrastructure with Real-Time Analysis and Advanced Encryption
Partners
Partner ApplicationBecome a Guardian Digital Worldwide Partner
Menu
HomeSolutions Cloud Email Security
EnGarde Cloud Email SecurityAdvanced Threat ProtectionMultitier Security & Policy ControlsIncident ResponseInformation ProtectionBy Platform
Office 365 Email SecurityGoogle G Suite Email ProtectionMicrosoft Exchange Email Protection By Size
Small & Medium BusinessBy Threats
PhishingSpear PhishingWhalingMalwareRansomwareBECEmail VirusesZero Day AttackWhy Guardian Digital About UsOur PhilosophyCustomer Success StoriesMedia CenterResource CenterOpen Source CommitmentOpen Source PhilosophyOpen Source AdvantageThe Guardian Digital AdvantageBlogIndustry Real Estate and Title CompaniesLaw FirmsHospitalityHealthcareFinancialInformation TechnologyPartners Partner Application
1-866-435-4689
Get Free Trial
Privacy Policy
Guardian Digital Privacy Statement
Last updated August 2020
Introduction
Guardian Digital Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. This statement details the steps we take to protect your personal information when you visit our website, mobile applications or various other sites hosted by our service providers on our behalf (collectively the “Sites”). It describes the personal information that we collect, the purposes for which we use such information, and your choices regarding our use of it. The steps we take to protect your personal information and how you can review and correct your personal information are also covered here. By accessing our Sites, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this policy.
Information Collected
Information collected directly from you.
Generally, you can visit Guardian Digital Sites without entering any personal information. On certain pages, we may ask you for personal information to provide a service or carry out a transaction that you have requested. The personal information we collect may include:
Contact details, such as your name, title, company/organization name, email address, telephone and fax numbers, and physical address;
Information about your company and job function;
Your email marketing preference;
Financial information (including credit card or account information);
Information such as your nationality and country of residence that allows us to determine your eligibility under export control regulations to receive information about certain technologies;
Information used to customize and facilitate your use of our Sites, including login and technical information;
Inquiries about and orders for our products and services;
Information that assists us in identifying the products and services that best meet your requirements;
Event registration information; and
Feedback from you about our Sites and our products and services generally.
If you make an application for a position with Guardian Digital, or if you are a current employee of Guardian Digital, we may collect the following information from you through our online portal:
Resume or CV, cover letter, previous work experience, educational background, type of employment sought, date available, employee referral, desired salary, travel preferences, information about your performance and career developments;
Identification, such as your passport number, expatriate status, government identification numbers (e.g. Social Security Number) where permitted, immigration status, nationality, and, where permitted, information concerning your heritage and ethnicity (for diversity monitoring purposes);
Bank account and payment details, compensation, and information about your health and sickness leave, work expenses, employee benefits and use of company resources, and your signature;
Photographs and personal details you provide in a profile; and
Any other information you submit to us, including any correspondences you may have with us.
You are not required to provide any of this information, but if you do not, we may not be able to provide you the requested service or complete your transaction.
Information collected automatically.
We collect information about your visit to our Sites, including what pages you view, the date and time you access the site, the number of bytes transferred, links you click, the materials you access, and other actions taken within Guardian Digital' Sites. On Sites that you enter with a user ID, we may connect this information with your identity to determine your potential interests in our products and services. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every Site you visit, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type and capabilities and language, your operating system, and the website from which you linked to our Site.
Information from other sources
We may obtain information about you from other sources, such as where your employer supplies your contact details though our customer portal. If you make an application for employment with us or accept employment with us, we may obtain information from third parties, including, to the extent permitted by applicable law, recruiters, employment research firms, identity verification services, the references you provide to us, websites and other publicly accessible information on the Internet. We may also receive information you submit to us through third-party websites, including through LinkedIn, and other publicly available sources. Where permitted by local law and with your consent, we may request background or credit checks from public authorities or financial institutions to evaluate your eligibility for employment or certain Guardian Digital positions or projects, as well as your medical information if required to evaluate your eligibility for employment benefits.
Use of information
Services and transactions. We use your personal information to deliver services or carry out transactions you have requested, such as providing information on Guardian Digital products, registering purchased products, processing product orders, handling warranty claims, providing product manuals, answering customer service requests, receiving Guardian Digital purchase orders and managing supplier information, facilitating use of our Sites, and so forth. In order to offer you a more consistent experience in your interactions with Guardian Digital, information collected by our Sites may be combined with information we collect by other means.
Website improvement. We may use your personal information to improve our Sites and related Guardian Digital products and services, or to make our Sites easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing our Sites to your particular preferences or interests.
Employment applications. We ask you for personal information in connection with a job application or inquiry, such as information about yourself, a resume or curriculum vitae. We may use this information throughout Guardian Digital and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates for the purpose of employment consideration. We will keep the information for future consideration unless you direct us not to do so. If you accept a position with Guardian Digital, we will retain this information as part of the employment relationship.
Employee portal.  If you are a Guardian Digital employee or contractor, we may offer portals or other pages on the Site to serve as a central resource for human resources functions and other functions related to the employment relationship. We may use your personal information to manage your rights, benefits, insurance plans, pensions, absences, compensation, training, leadership development, travel and other employment functions. We may also use your personal information, where permitted, for diversity monitoring, ethics and other compliance requirements. You may have the option to create an employee profile which is included in company directories and allows you to communicate and share information with other Guardian Digital employees and contractors.
Sharing of information
Disclosure of your personal information. Except as described below, personal information you provide to Guardian Digital through our Sites will not be shared outside of Guardian Digital and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission.
Disclosure to service providers. Guardian Digital contracts with other companies to provide services on our behalf, such as hosting Sites, sending out information, processing transactions, and analyzing our Sites. We provide these companies with only those elements of your personal information they need to deliver those services. These companies and their employees are prohibited from using that personal information for any other purpose.
Disclosure to distributors. In responding to a request made by you, we may share your personal information with companies that distribute our products or services. In those cases, we provide these companies with only those elements of your personal information they need to respond to your request, and these companies and their employees are prohibited from using that personal information for any other purpose. In some cases, we may seek your permission to share your information with distributors for marketing purposes other than responding to a request from you. However, we will not share your information for such marketing purposes unless we have obtained your express consent to do so.
Disclosure in connection with transactions. In connection with certain transactions, we may disclose some or all of your personal information to financial institutions, government entities, and shipping companies or postal services involved in fulfillment.
Disclosure in connection with acquisitions or divestitures. Circumstances may arise where for strategic or other business reasons Guardian Digital decides to sell, buy or otherwise reorganize businesses in some countries. Such a transaction may involve disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, or receiving it from sellers. It is Guardian Digital practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions.
Disclosure for other reasons. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with legal requirements or with legal process served on us, to protect and defend our rights or property, or in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of any individual.
Security
Guardian Digital is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access that are located in facilities to which access is limited. For Sites to which you log in, it is your responsibility to ensure the security of your password and not to reveal this information to others. When you move around a site to which you have logged in, or from one site to another that uses the same login mechanism, we verify your identity by means of an encrypted cookie placed on your machine.
Your choices and rights
In some cases, you can review and correct personal information you provide through our Sites by going to the page on which you provided the information. In all cases, you can make a request to review and correct your personal information collected via our public-facing Sites or ask Guardian Digital to stop using it visiting our Site at www.guardiandigital.com, clicking on  "Contact Us" and completing the online form. We may take steps to verify your identity before providing you access to your personal information. You can help us to maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying us of any change to your mailing address, phone number, or email address.
If you provided personal information to us as part of an application for a position with Guardian Digital or as part of your employment relationship with us and you have any questions about our information handling practices, please contact our Human Resources at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. or your local Human Resources Manager.
For residents of California
Through our site and partners, we receive data that you actively submit, as well as data that we track when you request information, or otherwise actively send us data. We usually collect data such as your name, email address, business address, telephone number, and other information related to the business you represent.
Guardian Digital adheres to rights of data subjects set out by CCPA. Residents of California upon verification have the right to:
The right to know which personal information is being collected
The right to know if personal data is being sold or shared, and to whom
The right to object to the sale of personal data
The right to access one's own personal information
The right to equal service and price, even for consumers who exercise their privacy rights
We may deny your deletion request if retaining the information is necessary for us or our service providers to:
Complete the transaction for which we collected the personal information, provide a good or service that you requested, take actions reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform our contract with you.
Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity, or prosecute those responsible for such activities.
Debug products to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.
Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise their free speech rights, or exercise another right provided for by law.
Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act (Cal. Penal Code § 1546 seq.).
Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when the information's deletion may likely render impossible or seriously impair the research's achievement, if you previously provided informed consent.
Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with consumer expectations based on your relationship with us.
Comply with a legal obligation.
Make other internal and lawful uses of that information that are compatible with the context in which you provided it.
To exercise these rights listed above, you can contact us by:
Calling 201-962-7300
Email us at pThis email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Mail us at: Guardian Digital, Inc.Attn: Data Controller103 Godwin AveSuite 314Midland Park, NJ 07432
Only you or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. You may also make a verifiable consumer request on behalf of your minor child.
You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. The verifiable consumer request must: Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative.
Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it. We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you. We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.
For residents of the European Union
If you reside in the European Union, you may have the right to ask Guardian Digital for a copy of your personal information; or to correct, delete or restrict processing of your personal information; or to receive a copy of your personal information in a structured, machine readable format.
In addition, you can object to the processing of your personal information in some circumstances and, where we have asked for your consent, you may withdraw it at any time. These rights may be limited, for example if fulfilling your request would reveal personal information about another person, if we have compelling legitimate interests, or if you ask us to delete information which we are required by law to keep.
We will retain your personal information only for as long as we need it for a legitimate interest, to fulfill your employment contract or perform a service at your request, or to meet a legal requirement, after which we will take steps to delete your personal information or hold it in a form that no longer identifies you.
You may request to fulfill any of these rights by completing our online form (see above instructions for access to the “Contact Us” link). If your request relates to information you provided as part of an application to or employment with Guardian Digital, please contact our Employee Service Center at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. or your local Human Resources Manager. If you have unresolved concerns, you have the right to complain to a data protection authority. The data controllers for your personal data are the Guardian Digital office to which you have made an application, the Guardian Digital office that employs you, as well as Guardian Digital, Inc.
International transfers of personal information
Personal information collected on our Websites may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Guardian Digital or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. If you are using our Sites to make an application to Guardian Digital or as part of your employment relationship with us, your information may be shared for legitimate business needs to our offices in other countries that may not have the same data protection standards as those in your country of residence. If you reside in a country that regulates such transfers, we take steps to adequately address the relevant requirements. For further information, you may contact us as described in the Your choices and rights section above.
Links to other sites
Our Sites may contain links to other sites such as professional and government organizations. We also link to third-party providers that host, maintain and operate on-line training or services. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by other sites.
Enforcement of this privacy statement
If you have questions regarding this statement or our handling of your personal information, please contact us. We will promptly address your concern and strive to reach a satisfactory resolution.
Changes to this privacy statement
Guardian Digital may occasionally update this privacy statement. If we do, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top and bottom of the privacy statement.
Safeguard Your Inbox
Let Guardian Digital help you accomplish your strategic business goals by safeguarding your most valuable assets — your employees — and your business information.
Have Questions or Comments?
+1 (866) GD-LINUX
hello@guardiandigital.com
Subscribe to our Behind the Shield Newsletter
Company
Customer Success StoriesAbout UsResource CenterMedia CenterCareersOur PhilosophyPartner ProgramsOur Open-Source Philosophy: Development Without LimitsOur SupportNewsletter Sign UpContact Us
Solutions
Advanced Threat ProtectionMulti-tiered Security & Policy ControlsSmall & Medium Business ProtectionEnGarde Cloud Email SecurityMicrosoft Office 365 ProtectionReal Estate and Title Companies: Secure Email Against Wire Transfer FraudLegal: Protect Email Against Cyberattacks and Data LeaksInformation ProtectionIncident ResponseSecure Gmail Against Phishing, Malware and Other Advanced AttacksOffice 365 Email SecurityGoogle G Suite Email ProtectionMicrosoft Exchange Email Protection
Services
Premium Support ServicesProfessional Engineering ServicesSign Up for Free TrialGuide: Choosing a Business Email Security Solution
Open Source Advantage
Open Source CommitmentOpen Source Security Advantagelinuxsecurity.comOpen Source Projects
Terms of Service/Privacy Policy/Cookie Statement/Site Map
© 1999–2020 Guardian Digital, Inc All Rights Reserved
